[27 Years Ago, the Himalayas, India]
Take the picture.
All these human remains... Unbelievable.
I wonder what those Japanese are looking for.
Stay here, and they'll be cursed.
Doctor.
I found something very interesting.
See?
This is in very good condition.
And there is still muscle fiber that remains.
Yes.
[Funeral, Shiharu Nanase]
[Hall 1]
Sir? Sir, one moment.
Sir!
Haruka.
What are you doing?
Who holds a funeral for their daughter,
when she's still alive?
I understand how you feel.
But you have to calm down.
Call off this ridiculous charade, now.
It's been four years.
We have to give her closure.
I saw Shiharu.
Let's talk outside.
Folks, please give us a moment.
Shiharu was there, at my thesis presentation!
It's not unusual to hold a funeral
for missing individuals.
But I saw her, after the flooding.
And I'm telling you, you were seeing things.
No, I'm certain that was her.
DNA can then mutate,
or become an inverted repeat sequence.
As DNA repeats,
it is more likely to undergo methylation.
A-Apologies.
DNA methylation affects
the transcription of genes,
through a remodeling of the chromatin.
I understand you can't accept it.
But, Haruka.
You cannot sacrifice your future
for my daughter's sake.
Professor Ishimizaki sees the talent in you.
You have to move on.
Focus on your research.
Shiharu is alive.
How can you assume otherwise?
You're her father.
Did you take your pills?
Quit treating me like I'm sick.
The clinic says you haven't visited.
Talking it out will help you process things.
Shiharu has passed on.
I apologize for the interruption.
Sir.
How much does he know?
Not a thing.
You're certain you can handle him?
Yes.
[A mystery spanning two centuries]
[The whereabouts of his missing step-sister]
A monster?
Yeah. It chased me into the mountains
when I was younger.
Which was just my excuse for getting lost.
Cute.
Didn't you ever make up stories like that?
Something to get your parents off your tail.
Maybe.
So, what about this monster?
Well, now I'm not so sure
if it really was an excuse.
Oh?
It's not so uncommon
for kids to conflate their lies with reality.
So that's probably what's happening here.
"The basis for
all true understanding and knowledge
is the capacity to observe."
That's a quote from Barbara McClintock.
A famous geneticist.
And here I thought
you were speaking wise words.
I just wanted to seem a bit smart.
Did you want to become a scientist?
I don't know.
It's coming down heavy.
- Let's hurry.
- Okay.
- Watch your steps.
- I will.
Professor Ishimizaki.
What a tough climb to make.
I hear this used to be an art museum?
You followed me?
Your father was worried about you.
Give him a call.
My "father", is it?
It's been seven years since my mother passed.
My step-father is practically a stranger now.
Grateful as I am for his support.
I saw the state of her coffin.
I assume that was your doing?
You must think Shiharu is dead as well.
But I can't accept that.
You don't have to.
There's no crime in believing she's alive.
But your belief in her,
and assuaging your father's worries,
are things you can do simultaneously, no?
[Nichie Pharmaceutical Headquarters]
How much of our stock
does Xin Ming Ah own?
They've already purchased 20% of our shares.
And they're about to acquire 10% more.
Can't we stop them?
They're a conglomerate from China.
It could lead to disastrous results.
What happens if we're bought out?
Can we keep "06-00" under wraps?
Barely any records remain
of such an old incident.
Check our archives again to be sure.
We must eradicate any evidence of "06-00".
How is your daughter?
Mari?
She's not doing well.
I can't even take her out in her wheelchair.
I see.
When I met her before...
Haruka.
Yes, sir?
Can you do a job for me?
What job?
I want you to analyze
a skeleton we found in India.
Pardon?
Have you heard of Roopkund?
The lake up in the Himalayas.
Sounds familiar.
It's a cursed lake, I'll tell you that.
They've found about 800 human remains
from that area alone.
800?
Was there a village nearby?
The lake is located
at an altitude of 5,000 meters.
That's no place
for a human village to thrive.
The bones themselves are attributed
to races all across Asia.
Their time of deaths don't match up either.
The 7th century, 10th century,
and some even date to the 19th century.
- You participated in the excavations, sir?
- Indeed.
Were these people making an offering?
Perhaps to a deity of sorts?
Even 27 years ago,
we never reached a conclusion.
Then why analyze a skeleton remain now?
Operations have resumed in India,
after they were cut short years back,
due to a lack of funding.
My colleagues there
reached out for my assistance.
How many remains are we analyzing?
Just one.
Scientists in India
have deduced these remains
are that of a young girl,
from over 200 years ago.
So?
Are you up for the challenge?
Yes, sir.
They say the lake is cursed.
According to the locals,
Roopkund afflicts any
who take its remains with them.
They say the remains themselves
are the skeletons of the damned.
Sounds like the perfect job for me.
Curses mean nothing
to a man who's lost everything.
I see.
You may think as such now.
But know this.
The world you see now,
is not the whole truth.
[Hyderabad, India]
Is there a god?
You went to Roopkund.
Who told you...
Say hello to the you of tomorrow.
[Roopkund]
[Do you wish to delete this folder?]
[Yes]
[Deletion in progress]
[I have acquired the remains.]
[Send]
Everything will be okay.
Nothing to worry about.
You'll be okay.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Are those the bones from the lake?
Yeah.
Need help with the analysis?
No, I finished up already.
Just waiting for the results.
These are from over 200 years ago?
Apparently. I'm having Itohara confirm it.
Then I'll plug in the data for you.
Thanks.
Sure thing.
- She's featured again.
- Who?
This woman. Is she that big of a deal?
[Kayoko Senba]
Kayoko Senba?
Yeah, she's a genius.
She's made advancements in neuroscience
most could only dream to achieve.
Wow...
I want to be as globally renowned as her.
Huh?
What's up?
- The DNA from these remains.
- Yeah?
We have a complete match to it
in our systems.
A complete match?
Yeah. The gene sequence is registered to...
Huh?
This laboratory.
What?
It's apparently sample number...
"T548".
[Shiharu Nanase]
Shiharu?
[log.1]
Impossible.
These bones...
[T548]
They can't be.
[Shiharu]
This was a sample I brought in
for orientation.
A piece of Shiharu's hair.
If the DNA sequence is a complete match,
then these bones from two centuries ago,
are Shiharu's.
Professor?
You have those, and I'll have these!
I can make a boat.
Burn the mill!
The humans seem like the real monsters here.
He must not know why they fear him.
To wonder why you've been born...
And there are no mistakes in these results?
Of course not. We were only double-checking.
See? Look at that radiocarbon dating.
These are definitely over two centuries old.
I see.
What's got you so down, rich kid?
Is Mr. Ishimizaki putting you to good work?
You alright?
Don't feel like research is your only option.
You can get a job, unlike aimless ol' me.
- Sorry, I have to go.
- Hey!
Make sure you get some sleep, alright?
Please leave a message after the tone.
This is Nanase, speaking.
Professor Ishimizaki, are you home?
I have something to tell you. It's urgent.
I'm heading over right now.
Professor, this is Nanase.
Sir, are you home?
Hello?
Professor Ishimizaki?
I'm coming in.
Professor?
Sir?
Hello?
Professor Ishimizaki?
[Incoming call: Nanase]
Sir?
P-Professor...
Professor.
Professor Ishimizaki!
Yes?
Yes, this is he.
What?
Ishimizaki has been...
Did you visit
Professor Ishimizaki's home often?
Yes.
I visited for advice
on research and analysis.
What were you doing last night,
until the time the Professor was found?
I was analyzing a specimen,
at the Professor's request.
Alone?
No. Until around 7PM,
I was accompanied by a junior of mine.
So you were alone, from 7PM till morning.
What are you trying to say?
Are you accusing me?
What sort of research do you do
with Professor Ishimizaki?
We're researching how patterns in DNA
has an effect on the genome.
Yes, come in.
Mayuzumi, a minute?
Sorry, we're almost done here.
You mentioned the Professor requested
you analyze a specimen for him?
Yes.
I was analyzing a skeleton
from a lake in the Himalayas.
You said it dated 200 years back.
What were the results of your analysis?
There was an error in my first pass.
I'll have to redo it.
I see.
Were the remains something of importance?
Yes, they would be to any researcher.
Well, the skeleton has been stolen.
What?
We went to check the laboratory
as you testified,
but nothing was found in the lab.
The associated DNA samples
have also vanished.
Dealing with the pressure from Xin Ming Ah?
Or with the death of your friend, Ishimizaki?
Sir, please back off.
Is his death tied to your father's incident?
Leave us.
Xin Ming Ah is buying your stock.
They'll eventually hold the reigns.
I will call the police.
Trying to rid yourself
of your father's bad legacy?
- Mr. Nanase, answer me!
- Back off!
You must be Maehara.
Right-hand man to President Nanase.
I hear he has you do the dirty work?
Nichie Pharmaceuticals
has nothing to say to you.
Your other employees
have already told me plenty.
They know nothing you could benefit from.
Make way, police.
When will they let us back in?
You cannot think of anything?
Even something small
you've noticed would help.
Hirama!
Hirama, sir.
I've got a real scoop for you.
If it's another celebrity scandal,
I don't need it.
How about a corporate one?
- I've heard enough conspiracies.
- Oh, it's no conspiracy.
This is my chance at redemption.
So you've said time and time again.
What's changed?
A corporate's misusing their capital
for illegal stunts,
and now a murder might be involved.
Come back to me after you have the evidence,
and not just hearsay.
This one's nothing like the rest, Hirama.
So you'll listen once I gather the evidence?
If it's a good story,
I'll treat you to sushi, girls, whatever.
I've had enough of hostess bars.
Especially the cheap ones.
You think I'm still a cheapskate?
I can afford better now.
Then it's a promise.
I'll bring you that riveting scoop.
Hey!
The hell's his problem?
Hirama, you have ties to Onodera?
Yeah. He used to work under me.
I don't hear great things about him.
I'm not surprised.
Can you believe he used to be an earnest guy?
He'd always work hard
to accomplish his goals.
Always pushing me to do better.
Seriously? That chronic blackmailer?
Yeah. I guess serious guys
tend to break heart early.
Not me, though.
Yeah, yeah.
While we were questioning Haruka Nanase,
the sample he was analyzing
at the Professor's request, vanished.
The culprit is likely the very same.
The university's security tapes
have already been overwritten.
There's nothing incriminating on them.
[Funeral, Akihiko Ishimizaki]
The world you see now,
is not the whole truth.
Dr. Senba has arrived.
I think all relevant data has been wiped.
Including the university security tapes?
Yes.
Though the cameras automatically reset
every 30 days,
this incident occurred
on the 17th day in that cycle.
How thorough.
Something's definitely up.
I'm betting on foul play.
Are you okay?
I'll drive you home.
It's fine. I'd rather walk.
What happened?
Talk to me.
I promise I won't doubt you.
Have you heard of Roopkund?
I believe so.
It's a lake, located in the Himalayas.
Professor Ishimizaki requested that I...
That I analyze one of the skeletons
found by the lake.
Ishimizaki asked you to do an analysis?
Yes.
Professor Ishimizaki passed away
before I could report
my findings to him.
Alright, take it easy.
Sit.
Breathe in, slowly.
Steady yourself.
Right.
So you analyzed these bones.
Yes.
According to my findings,
the DNA sequence of these remains
were a perfect match to Shiharu's sample.
It's true.
I believe you.
Really?
Can we talk more about this, alone?
I want to hear more.
Can you make time for me?
- Yes.
- Until then, keep it our secret.
We wouldn't want to accidentally
tarnish Ishimizaki's name, right?
Right.
Breathe in, slowly.
How about you visit the clinic?
I'll drive you there.
You don't believe me after all.
No, I'm just worried about you.
I don't believe it either.
For now, you're better off
keeping your findings to yourself.
"Don't raise a fuss about this", is that it?
You made yourself clear enough.
No, that's not it.
Haruka, there's something
you still don't know.
But this isn't the place to talk about it.
I see you're without a hammer today.
You are Haruka Nanase, yes?
I am Ishimizaki's niece, Yui.
- Oh, my...
- I am not here to ask for condolences.
I wish to ask about my uncle's death.
Shall we walk a bit?
You are my uncle's assistant, correct?
Yes.
Why did you go to my uncle's house that day?
You may be able to deceive the police,
but not me.
I know you're hiding something.
Wait.
Please, listen to what I have to say.
Mari is gone.
She went missing after my uncle's death.
Mari... Ishimizaki's daughter?
- Yes.
- In the wheelchair?
Yes.
She has disappeared.
- Does the police know?
- Of course.
Then they'll handle it.
Did you leave things to the police as well?
Were you calm when your sister disappeared?
Please.
If there's anything you know,
won't you share it with me?
What do you know?
Nothing, yet.
But I am one of the few people
who knew my uncle well.
Why don't we work together,
for the sake of our own goals?
Work together?
Yes.
"Cooperation is the key to humans surviving
a multitude of scenarios".
It's a quote from Nichola Raihani,
an evolutionary biologist.
Sorry.
I just wanted to seem a bit smart.
We're still unsure.
We've got the body, but no identity.
A monster?
We have no other leads!
We've only got the bones.
No decomposed matter in sight.